Thank you for watching!
Hi.
Seen, Ukka's, Delightful and Unhappy, Showroom.
That was kind of a lost battle.
I feel like I'm missing a voice.
Yes, good evening everyone. We're Ukka.
We are Uka, and we look forward to working with you.
I, Sora Chino, will be your facilitator today.
Please do so.
Then, please introduce yourself.
Yes, I'm Ruri Aoi, from Ukka. I look forward to working with you.
Today, I will be presenting the 185th Uguka's Yukari Fanal Showroom on a different day than usual,
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
And so, many good evening in the comments,
Thank you all for giving me after a long time.
Thank you very much.
The room is actually different this time.
Take a look.
I'm glad.
Tell him. Tell him.
Can I say this?
It's okay.
This is the room where my admirer used to sit.
What's his name? What group are you in?
Narisaka46.
We always deliver in this room.
I thought it was a familiar sight.
The room next door is the one we usually work in,
I have been working in the showroom studio since before the previous location was changed, but this is my first time here,
This is my first time here.
I am happy to be here for the first time.
So, I will be back in a different room,
It's Thursday again,
I hope you enjoy the show and I look forward to working with you again today.
Thank you very much.
Please do so.
So, we would like to have a spread time.
In order to get as many people as possible to watch the show, I'm going to tweet the announcement on our official Twitter page, so please tweet it to everyone.
How would you like to pose today?
Is this the pose of the day?
What will you do?
What do you think?
What should I choose?
It's just the two of us today, right?
Shall we pose as usual?
Then, what about a comment?
Shall I make a comment like, "We're both doing our best, so please come and see us.
Yes, I'll do that.
I'm being a total jerk.
I'm sorry.
You're cute.
Thank you very much.
Please comment like you're doing your best, so please come and see me.
But it's true.
It's raining today, so it's humid.
I was sweating a lot because I had a lesson earlier.
OK, I'm here! Okay, I'll leave it to you. Ready!
Is this the usual?
As usual.
Four, five, four, three, two, one.
That took a lot of time!
It took me quite a while.
Yes, it took a lot of time. So, I was probably able to get it taken,
I'll be tweeting a lot from now on, so please retweet me.
What is it? This.
It's a retweet symbol.
Oh!
This is a retweet mark.
Yes, yes, yes.
Retweet mark.
Please do it.
Please do.
Yes, please. So, here is the first section.
Yukari Funa 15-minute status report.
Yay!
So, Yukarifuna, I'm going to talk freely about recent events,
Next week, Yukka's first major single will finally be released,
I'd like to show you that we are a group that can keep time like major artists,
We would like to have a free talk about group and individual events in exactly 15 minutes,
However, at our meeting earlier, we were told that we do not need 15 minutes this time,
I would like to enjoy myself without worrying too much about the time.
I would like to have fun without worrying too much about the time.
I'd like to have fun without worrying too much about the time. So, let me start from here.
On June 3, Rina and Ruri's first birthday solo live was held.
Yay!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
Well, it went by so fast.Well, it all happened so fast.
I had known we were going to do it for quite a while,
I knew we were going to do it long before, and we had already decided on the songs,
It all happened so fast. I was surprised.
It was fun. It was my first time.
It was like there were only people who came to see me,
In such a situation, everyone worked very hard to make their voices heard,
It was a warm and happy space. I want to go back.
No, you're right.
Yes, you're right.
Did any of you guys go?
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Yes, I did. I went too.
Yes, I did.
The birthday party was fun. I cried.
It was really good.
It was Yuki's birthday solo live.
Everyone is praising it.
They said it was the illustrations on the cards, etc.
I see. For visitors, you know.
Like the bonus cards.
I drew them all by hand, one by one.
What do you mean?
I drew animal characters.
Animal type? Not the words.
I wrote the letters together, and I'm not very good at drawing,
I'm not very good at drawing, so I tried my best to use what I'm good at.
Then there was the gummy skirt. The gummy skirts were great.
Oh, thank you very much.
What is a gummy skirt?
I was about six months old. I ate a lot of gummy bears and made a skirt out of them.
Just like that. Lots of gummy bears.
That's on the official Instagram, right? The skirt.
Please everyone go take a look. Insta.
Please.
I heard it was written by Rižu. Rižu-chan wrote it?
I wrote one for each member.
She also wrote one for you.
Thank you very much. I'm sorry.
You too, Rižu-chan.
I see.
Is there anything you were particular about? The center.
But overall, I wanted to make it cute and persistent,
I wanted to make it cute, or rather, pink,
So I chose songs that I like and that are cute.
Would you say the content was pretty heavy?
I think it was a bit heavy.
Sakamaru-san. It's your first time here. Hello.
Good evening.
And you, Shine-chan.
I'm Ika.
Good evening.
It was a trigger, wasn't it?
I sang at Kikkake.
It's a song by Nogizaka-san, isn't it?
That's right. I wanted to sing this song for sure,
When was it? We talked about it in the showroom,
I wanted to sing it, so I put it in first.
It's nice.
Gachikoi Factory was in there.
I didn't expect you to include it,
Which song?
Girls Rule.
This is another song by Nogizaka,
I was impressed when they played "Girls' Rule",
I was able to hear "Gachikoi Factory.
I didn't expect to hear it,
I was so happy.
I also went to see the live performance.
Before the show started, they said, "My Wife Goal"?
I was so surprised. What is that?
What was that?
I was so surprised. But I want you to listen to me,
I like to watch TikTok a lot,
I often watch TikTok, and I saw Asuka Saito's graduation video,
The audience was calling out "my wife, no, no, no, no, no, she's my wife,
I was surprised to hear the audience chanting "my wife, no, no, no, she's my wife,
I was just thinking that there was such a call,
I was wondering if there was such a call, because they were saying it from the beginning before they started,
I could hear it live.
I don't think he was the one who said it,
It was a fresh feeling and I was surprised.
I thought to myself, "He's calling for my wife? I thought.
I was surprised.
I'm glad.
I'm famous for my calls this year.
I see. Is he quite famous?
Yes, he is. I go to a lot of their shows,Yes, that's right. I go to a lot of live concerts,
I see a lot of shouting. Everyone is shouting.
They are shouting.
No, no, no, no.
I see. It was a fresh feeling. It was fun.
It was fun.
How about next year? Do you want to do it?
I would love to do it. I don't know about next year,
A little bit of a gap?
I've been like this for a long time, so I'd like to be a little cooler.
I don't know.
Part of the event was Lina's birthday,
Did you go to Lina's birthday party? Did you go to Lina's birthday party?
How about you?
I went.
Probably.
I guess many of you went.
Good evening.
I also went to some of the events. And Lina's birthday.
How was it?
My impression is very simple. I cried.
I cried a lot.
I think I was crying pretty early on.
I cried so much that I went to the back to get tissues.
No way.
I went to the back to get a tissue,
Rina's father and mother were there next to me,
They were crying. I saw them crying,
I saw them.
I don't know, I was thinking too much,
I saw Lina crying, and she didn't seem to have any tissues or anything,
So I went to get them for her,
I went to get a bag of tissues,
I was going to take that with me,
I was going to take the bag of tissues, but if I took them, when Lina came to throw up, there would be no tissues left,
I'm sorry, but I had to carry the tissues with me.
So I gave them to Lina's father and mother and said, "Here are some tissues,
They laughed so much.
They laughed and said, "Thank you very much,
And they took it,
The next time I saw Lina,
I said, "Thank you very much for the tissue from your mother,
and she gave me a neat little bag of unopened tissues,
I think she and her mother were making them together.
It's funny, isn't it?
I still have her mom's toque,
You still have it?
I still have it.
At some concert, my mom was talking with Momochan's mom before the concert started,
She was talking with Momochan's mother before the show started, and then Rina's mother started talking to her,
Rina's mother asked me, "Are you the mother of someone related to Momochan? Rina's mother asked me if I was her mother,
I said, "I'm Rina's mother and I'm looking forward to working with you,
I thought, "Oh my God, I'm Rina's mother,
I thought, "Oh my God, she's like this.
I thought it was cute.
Rina's mother was very kind to me,
I heard that kind of talk, too.
It's so cute.
It's Lina's mom talk and Lina's dad talk.
It's interesting, isn't it? Really.
But it's similar to both of them, isn't it? I mean, they're both interesting.
I understand. It's a combination of both, kindness and fun.
I know I've gone too far from the story of Lina's birth,
I talked about Lina's mother and father,
I also talked about Ultrasoul.
I wanted to see it.
I wanted to see it, but it was in the back, so it was just sound,
I thought it would be a lot of fun,
It was really loud.
Ultrasoul.
Boom! It was amazing.
It was amazing.
Once again, the sense of unity in the venue was amazing.
It was interesting.
Lina's performance had more of a narrative or storyline,
I was quite moved,
There were also songs about going to college or going on to higher education and what they want to do,
I could really relate to it,
I was about to cry.
With the uniforms and the tiles.
Maybe that's it.
I was so moved.
You were quite moved.
It was a good time for Ultrasoul.
That's right.
Thanks for the two birthdays.
So, if there is another one next year, please do your best.
I will do my best.I will do my best.
So, this birth story is over for now,
Now for the next story,
On June 21, we will be releasing our first major single "One, Two, Little Love!
We are currently holding release events.
First, on June 10, Tatsuki Tachikawa of Lilybella Report will be performing,
and on Sunday, June 11 at Kanda Clock.
Thank you very much.
How is it?
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
Tatsuki Tachikawa has been delivering a lot of the concerts, hasn't he?
This is my second time,
I feel safe, and it's nice to be in a public square.
You can feel the nature.
Even the little kids were enjoying the water coming out from the bottom,
I thought it was nice and felt good.
I was glad it didn't rain,
It didn't rain too much.
Also, the benefit parties have been a bit elaborate lately,
I was doing something unusual,
What do you call this?
A handbag?
It's not a handbag.
Not hand magic.
Magic hand.
Like patting someone on the shoulder with a magic hand,
Like in the Tail Bindo song, the back-pushing video,
Touching, thumping, and banging,
That kind of thing was unusual and fun,
And the Governor of Lalaport Cube and the Masked Lady Clock,
Thank you very much for all the food and goodies you gave us.
We all enjoyed them very much.
Thank you very much.
Did you receive anything from the Masked Lady Clock that the rest of us usually eat?
Yes, she gave us Kiritoremon,
And Calorie Mate.
We also received Wiser.
Thank you very much.
And we still have the next one coming up,
Friday, tomorrow?
Tomorrow.
We also have a talk show,
We also have events on Saturday and Sunday,
What's that? Yes, there is, isn't there?
Yes, there are.
Please come and join us.
I'll make a proper announcement later. Please do.
Yes, that's right,
This is Wither's first single,
WONDERLAND W will be released,
The performance video of this song is now available on YouTube,
So today, you can watch it,
So I would like to watch it with you today.
I would like to watch it with you.
Is this a good time?
Here is the performance video!
I love this horse.
He can hear me when I talk like this.
It's nice.
This town is cute.
Yeah, it is.
Can I crack up?
No, no, no.
Cocktails are good.
You're putting your hands in the air.
It's a little different from before the show.
Yes, yes, yes.
I have long bangs.
You're right, it's long.
It was hard to do here, wasn't it?
It was hard to get them aligned.
I practiced a lot.
Everyone else practiced too.
Everyone else is practicing, too.
It's nice.
This studio is cute, isn't it?
It's so cute.
If I could do a heart, it would sound pretty close to the edge.
I really like Hula's outfit.
Really?
I decided on this one myself.
She said she'd be the first to think of it.
I don't care what it is.
I don't know.
This?
Something like this.He said he kind of liked it this way.
It's strange.
Yes, yes, yes
Hula-chan's melody
her mouth is smudging
It's got some kind of campas in it, so it looks wonderful and beautiful, doesn't it?
Yes, you notice it, don't you?
Surprising, isn't it?
Aren't you surprised?
You didn't?
I hadn't seen it before.
Wonder in the love
You know, you know, you know, you know
You know, I like this song.
I love this song.
♪ In the season of newborns, on the way, pearls in the air ♪
I painted the tip of my pinky finger, the flower I wish to be shigure
Oh, it's coming. It's coming.
It's coming.
You don't put your hand on my shoulder anymore, do you?
That's right.
I'm too old for that.
I wonder if he's all right.
I'm always afraid of him.
You mean you're not scared?
I love Sora's anxious face when she was a child.
Do you think she'll be okay? Will I be able to enter? Like that.
Yes. So this was a formant video.
Yes, it was. Thank you very much.
What do you think? Do you have any favorite parts?
This is definitely going to grow.
It's definitely going to grow.
Let's stretch it out a bit. Okay, then.
Okay.
Next week?
Next week, the 21st.
The 21st. It's almost ready to go on sale.
We need to get things going a little more.
We have one minute left.
There's one minute left, but I'd like to extend it by about three minutes.
That's right. Longer.
It's a work of art, isn't it?
It's true.
What was your favorite part of the past?
Oh, but the pretending to do the "cha-cha-cha-cha" together before the otsukare?
I like her sense of togetherness.
And the rest,
The clean front.
Yes, yes.
The way the sound changes is important.
It's like a cute little "cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha.
Please go ahead.
Ah, thank you very much.
I knew that.
And, as coment mentioned earlier,
There's this part where he turns around with this whisper,
I always wondered if it was okay.
Sometimes. When I performed it for the first time, it was something like that,
When Rui turned around,
I was trying to forget that sound, and recently I've been able to meet Rui.
You know why we don't get along?
I didn't mind it and didn't cut it off, but it became something.
When the mv was released, I suddenly had one, but not before, that's why it was strange.
I was just a little bit nervous, but I was right.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but it's a good idea.
I finally got it... and my voice is finally stable.
There was the Wander Building in space... that I couldn't support it at all.
Is there anything you like about it?
I'm only writing this once in a while... but I wonder if you could tell from the rates.
I wonder if you got the rate from everyone.
I'd love to know what your favorite part is.
I'd love to know what you like about it.
It's all so cute!
I saw it all in slow motion.
I see.
I understand recently, somehow.
I came to find out later.
Yes, I did.
I like the clover part, too. Oh! Which one is it? The big clover one?
I'm holding it like this downstairs. I like this. Ah!
It's like, uh, tracing the forest. You're tracing. Yes, it is.
I'm actually working on a clover downstairs, too. This clover that you and I found, that you and I found..,
I'm doing a clover, one of the four-leaf clovers. The top one, too.
The top one is doing a four-leaf clover like this.
I like the way you squat with the glass pen. I understand, I understand. That's right.
The arch.The arch.
This one. This one? This one. This one is nice, too.
Oh, we like rust. Oh, my. Thank you very much. I'm glad.
It's nice. You should come to see Sabi. That's right. There are many unexpected highlights, so please come back and
performance video, and please pay attention to the live performance as well. Please do so.
Yes, I know I'm a little late, but this was the 15-minute YUKAI DEHUNA status report.
Okay, so I would like to move on to the next one. Today, I would like to do a project like this. The title is
Uguka no Yuukai de Funa Half & Half!
Okay, so I would like to explain the rules. Now, one by one, I'm going to ask each user a two-choice question.
The question can be about anything, but we aim for the voting result to be 50-50, i.e., half and half.
Two people will each ask a question, and the one who is closest to 50-50 wins.
For example, let's take a very simple example.
The person who is closest to the 50-50 winner wins. It's like that.
Then we ask a question like, "What is your favorite food? We will ask a question like "What is your favorite food?
Let's think of a question.
Shall we think of a question? Yes, let's think of a question. What should we do?
It's so difficult, isn't it? This is really hard. I couldn't think of anything at all.
I'm stumped.
Hmmm... What would be good?
50-50 is so difficult, isn't it?
It's so difficult.
I wonder.
Oh, but that's... Oh, but surely that's right.
I don't know.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, wait.
Uh...
How interested are you?
Um...
Can I ask you one question?
Do you know what this is?
Yes, I do.
So, is it a different kind?
This one's a tea.
I'll leave them all in a row.
Well, pick one.
I've decided. Okay, I'll write it down.
I'll write the questions. I'll write the questions now.
I'll be back in a minute.
Thin.
It's so thin.
Look.
He's right behind you.
Where is it? Where?
Behind you on the left.
Where? Where?
Oh, there it is. There it is.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, that's okay. I don't need it.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
It just flew away.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
This is definitely...
No, I don't want it.
Where'd he go?
Where'd it go?
Oh, he's gone.
He's gone. He's gone.
He's gone. He's gone. He's gone.
Did he go somewhere?
Wait a minute.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, it's obvious.
No, I just thought of it.
I see.
Wait a minute, I don't know the kanji.
I'm sorry for using hiragana.
Hiragana!
I'm really sorry, hiragana sucks!
Yes, may I?
Yes, okay.
Here we go.
Which would you go to at the end of summer?
So, Okinawa and Hokkaido.
One is Okinawa and two is Hokkaido.
It's the end of summer. The point is.
I see.
Yes, I see.
Then, please vote.
1 is Okinawa, 2 is Hokkaido.
Okay.
What do you think?
It's the end of summer.
Okinawa or Hokkaido at the end of summer?
Which would you prefer? Sora would be.
Hokkaido.
Why?
Because it might snow too much in Hokkaido in winter.
On the other hand, would you like to go there now?On the other hand, is it like over there at the moment?
Mr. Saitama.
It's Chuken. Good evening.
I'm Chukan.
Well, I guess it's time to end.
Five, four, three, two, one, now!
How's it going?
Where is it? The result.
Here it comes!
Something is totally different!
Everyone's in Okinawa, not Hokkaido?
Do it!
The winner is Hokkaido.
60% of the respondents were from Hokkaido.
What? That doesn't sound very half-and-half, does it?
It was 6 to 4.
Oh, no.
That's strange.
Oh, dear.
I couldn't get a "one heart, two minds.
Too bad.
So, it's 6 to 4.
I was 6-4, roughly.
Yes.
Then I would like to go next.
Here is my subject.
Speaking of tea, 1. Soukenbicha 2.
It's a bit of a toss-up, isn't it?
I don't drink tea, so I have no idea which is more popular,
I don't drink tea, so I have no idea which is more popular, but this is what I came up with, so I'll give it a try.
So, let's start the voting!
I don't even know the difference between the two.
What do you think?
I think the tea looks like barley tea.
I see.
So tea is green tea?
I'm going to be biased. Oh no.
I'm going to lose.
Oh no.
The one with the smallest difference in evenness is the winner.
I want to win 6 to 4.
Well, I think it's time to go.
Ready.
Five, four, three, two, one.
That's it.
Now, please.
You're still late for the celebration channel.
Wow! Yay, yay!
Yay! Not at all!
Yeah!
Six versus what? No, it's not.
It's not six, it's what, seven to three?
Oh, no! We lost!
The winner is Ruri!
Yay! We won!
What!
Ruri-san 23, Sora-chan 25, Sora-chan 35!
That's too much!
Yes, I did.
Oh! So we can go around again! Yay!
Let's go around again!
Oh, no!
What should we do?
I think I'll just do the one from everyone else.
Oh, it's so different.
Oh, I see.
That's so frustrating!
What should I do?
But I like this one too.
Wait a minute. I'm blind.
Have you decided?
Yes, I have.
This one?
But what happens now?
But this is good. There might be too many.
You're lost, aren't you?
I'm really confused.
This is still a lot.
Ahhh...
Ah, but this...
I don't want to do it because I think there'll be people who'll say, "That's not it.
Let's go this way.
Okay, then.
Wait.
Got it.
Oh, I made a mistake again.
Oh, it won't answer.
Yes, I did.
Five.
Yes, which one would you rather have for a snack?Yes, which would you rather eat for a snack?
1 is gummy and 2 is chocolate.
Oh, uh...
Which is it?
This is pretty, pretty obvious. I can't tell,
I'm sure.
Isn't it the packaging?
Yes, for sure.
Well then, everyone, please try it,
If you think gummy bears are the way to go for a snack, please vote for 1.
If you want to eat chocolate as a snack, please choose 2.
Then, let's start the documentary!
Oh, man.
This is good.
I really can't write kanji. I'm really sorry.
Well, I guess it's about time.
Isn't it early? A little.
Almost there. I'm impatient.
I apologize.
Which way? Which one?
Look, it doesn't have to be gummy bears because I like gummy bears. Gentlemen.
Please don't be so discerning.
This is gobble gobble.
I don't know what to do. If this is the best gummy bear.
You. Maybe.
Well, I guess it's time.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Closing.
What's the result?
There's going to be a lot of 1s.
What?
It's the same as before.
What? Oh, no.
Is it chocolate? Aren't they all gummy?
I'm chocolate, too.
Chocolate.
I am chocolate, too.
I thought you were gummy.
So it's six to four.
It's the same as before.
Oh, six to four.
I'll go next.
Sorry for the hiragana first.
This way.
If you eat noodles, you should eat 1. soba noodles and 2. udon noodles.
I think this is a good choice.
I am SOKUTO.
Let's start voting.
By the way, Sora, which do you prefer?
I choose Soba.
Because udon requires a lot of chewing.
It is thicker.
My jaw gets tired. I have a weak jaw.
I have a weak jaw, so I chew a lot.
That's why I prefer soba.
I prefer udon.
I don't really like soba, I prefer udon.
When I think of noodles, I think of ramen, pasta, and udon.
I like Soba the most.
I like Soba the best.
Wow, that's pretty obvious.
You seem to know what you're talking about.
Yes, it is.
Okay, then?
Okay, five, four, three, two, one, done!
Now which one? Please!
Please!
What do you think? What do you think? What do you think?
Oh, my God!
That's pretty good, isn't it?
50 to 4!
Oh, my God!
Well, then, isn't this the bad one? This one.
Yay!
Five 2.3. That's great!
Yay! Yay, guys! Yay!
So, Akane-san won the second round.
Thank you very much. That's great!
Wow, that's great!
You're so cute with your big mouth.
Please calm down.
I'll calm down. I'll calm down.
Congratulations on the one to four.
I see. Half and half.
Yay!
I'm so happy. Thank you very much.
Yes, so it was fun, wasn't it?
So, that's all for now, Yukari Ofuna Half & Half Conan.
Yay!
Let's go to the next one.
Okay, just a little bit more.Yes, we are almost there.
Now, here is the next project.
The title is Yukari Ofuna Ukka GPT!
Yay!
It's called Yukari Ofuna Ukka GPT,
Have you heard of GPT?
I recently learned about it.
Recently learned about it?
It's a service in which artificial intelligence instantly answers any questions you may have,
This time, I'd like to do UkaGPT to compete with chat GPT.
Please feel free to ask us any questions in the comments.
Anyway, we will answer you as soon as possible.
I will do my best.
By the way, since Ebichu GPT was well received,
This was after we decided to do it in Uka as well.
As for the showroom, we are more senior than you,
Thank you, Ebichu.
That's a lie. Thank you very much, Ebichu.
Thank you very much.
Yes, that's why.
Everyone, any questions or anything you want to ask us, Uka GPT, in the comments.
Please leave your comments.
I'll do my best to answer right away anyway.
I'm definitely not good at this.
I think too much.
No need to think. It's intuition.
That's right. I'll do my best to answer by intuition, so please ask your questions.
Okay, then.
What's the weather going to be like tomorrow? I heard.
Then, when Rure reads it out, I'll be there?
Okay, I'll do that.
Then, hey!
Wookah GPT, what's the weather tomorrow?
Sunny.
Is this how it's going to be? That's what this is?
Okay, I got it.
Let's try our best to answer as many questions as possible like that.
This is the last project.
Okay, I'll do my best. Let's do our best.
Let's do our best.
Look at this. I'm going to say something irrelevant.
It's a turnoff.
It's true.
I'm a sucker.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Oh, hey! Wookah GPT.
Hey.
Directions for tomorrow's DDV.
Oh, there's no answer.
Sinjuk.
Aren't you a little late?
There's a time difference.
I've got a lot on the brain.
Sorry about the time lag.
So if it's too hard, it freezes.
That's right.
Yes, PT Yukajin.
What's tomorrow's ice cream?
Tomorrow it's Haagen-Dach.
Wasn't it a little bit like that?
I don't know if it's similar.
Actually, Haagen-Dazs is.
Yes, sir.
Hey, UkaGD, how do you make curry?
You put water and curry powder.
No garnish?
No garnish.
It's delicious without garnish.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Hey, YukaGPT!
YukaGPT!
Let's decide what we're having for dinner tonight.
Shrimp for dinner tonight.
Shrimp! YukaGPT wants shrimp!
What's next?
Hey, UkaGPT, what temperature do you want the air conditioning on?
What? Air conditioning...
What temperature do you want the air-conditioning on?
What temperature do you want the air conditioning on?
10 degrees!
It's cold! Isn't it cold?
10 degrees.
Be careful not to freeze.
It's cold, isn't it?
Next.
Hey! UkaGPT, what's the in-group teaching?
I made a mistake. I couldn't read the kanji. Sorry.I made a mistake. I couldn't read the kanji. I'm sorry.
Um, wait a minute.
Oh, there's quite a lot of dinner.
Hasn't everyone eaten yet?
Oh, wait, you're not going to tell us why? Because you're going to tell us why, too?
Is it called "shut GPT"?
I see.
What's the reason?
Well, so, for example, if it's Häagen-Dazs, like I just said,
You say why Haagen-Dazs is good, right?
Oh, I have a reason.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Uncle?
You're late.
Next, oh, hey, yuka GPT.
Yes, sir.
Is it a crime to spank?
Peeing is fine.
Oh, why?
Why not?
Peeing is good.
No, it's broken. It's broken.
It's not broken.
This thing is broken.
I see. So it's good for now.
Yes, it is. The oshimashi is good.
It's good. Oshimashi is good. But not for "oshi-hen"?
Peeing is a little sad, isn't it?
But, it's still not unpleasant, so it's more like a win-win-win.
I see.
Yes, I see. Ujikawapitei.
What hat should I wear tomorrow?
Let's wear Rina's birthday hat tomorrow.
Because Rina will be happy.
Oh, perfect. And with a reason.
That's what I'm talking about.
It depends a bit on GPT until the movement.
Oh, Hey!
Yes.
Name three things you find attractive about Ugka.
Cute, like, love.
I think she's a little broken.
I think she's starting to break.
Cute, like, love.
I was saying like, love.
I'm not typing, right?
Next.
Hey!
Ugakkapithee.
What's the highlight of the new song?
This one.
What do you think?
It has movement.
I'm not explaining. It has movement.
Do you understand this?
I do.
This is it.
I can't say what it is yet,
It's just Mihi,
I'm Mihi, so I'll take this one, please.
I see.
Yes, I see. Ukaji P.T.
Yes, sir. Tomorrow, long sleeves, tomorrow, short sleeves.
Tomorrow will be good for tank tops.
Tomorrow will be sunny, so tank tops will be good.
You really want me to wear a tank top. Ukaji Petey.
Tank tops will be good.
Yes, it is. It's going to be sunny tomorrow.
Okay, then, Hey!UkaGPT.
Where's the Wonder Little Love showing?
Please repeat that.
UkaGPT.
Where is the highlight of Wonder Little Love?
What is the highlight of Wonder Little Love?
Before the chorus
where they are making this circle.
where people are coming in and out of the circle.
The other day, me and Liz Murahoshi collided with each other.
That kind of accident is also a highlight of the show.
It's not a circle, it's an arch.
It's an arch.
It was an arch. I'm sorry.
Oh, we collided, didn't we?
Yes, there was a bang.
It went "poof".
I have no idea.
I was doing this on camera and pretending that Riju was coming toward me,
But I couldn't see her because she was facing backward,I couldn't see him because he was coming in backwards at that time,
And I couldn't avoid it either, so I got hit with a bang.
That's what happened.
I see. I finally understand.
Yes, I finally understand. So, I guess we have one last question each.
Yes. Is there?
Hey, UkaGPT.
I'm thinking of skipping work tomorrow, but please make up a good excuse.
What is your reason for skipping work tomorrow?
I'm skipping work.
What is your reason for skipping work?
What is your reason for skipping work tomorrow?
I might have a breakdown.
I have a breakdown. I have a breakdown.
You probably shouldn't skip work tomorrow.
You mean you should go to work tomorrow.
Yes. So let's go to the last one, shall we?
Yes, sir. Last question.
It's a tough one. Rust.
Oh, shit. I fell.
Sorry. I'm playing with a robot.
Let's see...
Hey!
Hi~.
They are each other's good points, then,
Please tell me what is good about Ucuka's Akane Sora.
The good things about Ucuka's Akane Sora are
Kind, cute, persistent, good dancer, good singer, everything is perfect !
Girl!
That's all I have to say,
Huh?
My good point.
So, that's all for now, I'm Yukkari-de-fu, Ukkajin-beetee.
I forgot something. I forgot something.
Huh? I was waiting for you to tell me, but I was quite nervous to be told now.
Yes, I was. So, that was Ukkajin Beatty.
Well, I think I'll listen to more.
The 185th episode is coming to an end in the blink of an eye.
Yes. So, I would like to make some announcements.
First of all, here is the first one.
On July 14 and 15, Fishbowl and Uka will have a tourman night in Okinawa.
Okinawa, right?
The place is Output Okinawa.
The tickets are now on sale to the general public, so please come and join us. We are looking forward to seeing you there.
I heard there are only a few more days left. We are waiting for you.
We are waiting for you.
Let's spend the summer.
But this is just another thing we decided the other day. Various things.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's pretty Okinawan, isn't it?
What? There are some customs that are unique to this two-person show,
Please come and join us. Please come.
Please come.
And the day after this 2-man show, we will be performing at Spark 2023 in Yama no Gakko (Mountain School).
Yay!
We get to see each other for 3 days in a row.
I'm so happy.
I've been coming here for a long time.
I've been coming all this time.
Well, the timetable hasn't been released yet, but I'll be performing on Sunday the 16th,
I will be performing on Sunday the 16th.
There will be many idols from Starlast and many other idols as well,
Please come and join us. We are looking forward to seeing you.
We're looking forward to seeing you.
Okay, next.
Uka's mama's live concert is coming up.
First, Shibuya Beats on Saturday, September 30, then Tokyo Kinema Club on Saturday, October 14,
And on January 21, 2024 at Ebisu Liquid Room.
We have a lot of events lined up,
We are aiming for Soul Doubt at all three venues,
Please come and join us. Please come.
Please come to all three venues.
And here is the release information.
Next, we will have a talk show at Tower Records Shinjuku Store tomorrow, June 16.
On Saturday the 17th, there will be a release event at La La Court Niimiri.
This one is in Sapporo.
Yay!
There will be Sapporo, and on this day, a new song that has not been released yet,
We are looking forward to seeing you all there. We are looking forward to seeing you there.
The show will start at 1:00 pm. Don't forget, everyone.
There is only a portion of the show, but there will be another performance on the 20th. We will be performing a new song, so please come.
It's not part of the program, is it?
Yes, it is. Please come.
And on June 20, a weekday Tuesday, there will be a release event at the Magnet rooftop in Shibuya,
We will have a release event on the rooftop of Magnet in Shibuya.
This is only a part of the night.
Yes. The next day is the release day.
On the first release day, we will have a live concert at J Square Shinagawa.
This is also only a part of the night.This is only part of the evening as well.
This is the day of the launch, and I hope everyone can enjoy it with us.
And a little time has passed,
On Saturday, June 20, Arino Hashimoto's 3rd anniversary.
The next day, June 25th, we will have a release event at a certain place in Tokyo.
This 25th will be the last one, so please come and join us. Please come.
Please come.
We will be posting various information on Twitter from time to time, so please check back.
Please check it out. And June 23rd, right?
There will be an online signing.
I will be signing clear files this time.
Please check it out.
Please do.
Yes, please. So, I would like to check the final ranking as well as the final ranking.
Yes.
First of all, fifth place goes to the Iwaryu aspiring members.
Thank you very much.
Next, fourth place,
That's not right. I'm sorry. I made a mistake. I'll stop again.
Fifth place, Mr. Birdcage.
Thank you very much.
Fourth place, Shibarie-san.
And, in third place, Iwaryu Shikkotai-san.
Thank you very much.
In second place, Ken-san.
In first place, Risaki-san.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now.
So, the next broadcast will be back on the usual day of the week, Wednesday, July 5, at 7:00 p.m.
Please mark your hearts and subscribe to our favorite programs so that you don't miss any more.
Please also check out our private broadcasts as well.
That brings us to the end of the 185th episode of Ukka's Yukarifuna Showroom.
This time, there will be no review meeting, so I would like to end at this time.
Thank you very much for watching today.
Thank you very much.
I hope you had a good time.
Since there will be no review meeting, is it okay if I extend the time a little bit?
Just a little bit.
Thank you very much.
We will also perform a new song.
That's right.
Tomorrow, we'll be wearing plain clothes.
Can I say something?
Tomorrow I will be wearing my own clothes, so I hope you can look forward to that as well.
It's a new outfit, so I think it will be easy to wear.
I hope you will enjoy it.
I hope you will tell me after work or after school.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Really.
It's Thursday.
Yes, it is.
I know it's a bit of a tiring day, but thank you for seeing me.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. Hi.
What is it?
It was sweat in class today.
Now, when you said Thursday, I thought there was something going on.
This is quite a surprise.
Surprise, surprise, surprise.
Let's do our best.
Next Thursday.
So, thank you all very much.
That's all for now.
Bye bye.
Thank you very much.